you know the fact that you know you love
your parents and um you know and you
always love them you'll have
unconditional love for them but it
sometimes it gets frustrating so um when
you were growing up did were did you
have a lot of friends did were did you
um you know you seem to be a smart guy
and usually smart guys are you know by
themselves kind of thinking and
tinkering stuff when they're kids and
not really associate with a lot of
people were you that person or were you
the opposite where did you have a lot of
friends did you have a lot of support
when you were growing
up I think in each cuz I like I said we
moved around a little bit so in each
area I moved I had like two or three
really good friends I didn't really have
anybody that you know didn't like me
yeah but I wasn't like that guy that you
know went to all these parties and had a
lot you know you know what I mean so I
had a um I had two or three people that
I used you know in each aspect of life
that I
would hang out with or you know do stuff
with and every single one of them at
this point is pretty successful so I was
hanging out
[Music]
hey folks my name is Ryan Perez I am
owner and founder of bow TI creative and
of course I'm the lovely host of um
hustlez own.tv so how are you guys doing
today um today is a great day yesterday
was my birthday and I turned 34 I feel
old um I feel that I need like greater
responsibility almost like I need to buy
a dog so I can go and walk it um I don't
know I'm just not a fan of this whole
34y old thing and um but we we'll we'll
get through it um so folks my name is
Ryan Perez owner and founder of Biv
hustle own uh TV and branding jim.com so
um hustle uh uh B creative we are uh
digital agency that um uh that builds
branding project or uh that builds uh uh
branding packages for people uh we also
build uh online businesses we don't call
them websites because our websites do
more um and then we also just launched
um ww. branding jim.com giving
entrepreneurs unlimited graphic design
um so you no longer have to hire a
graphic designer do all your
Communications just pay for U you know
$3.99 and you get all unlimited graphic
design and then of course hustles own TV
we are the world's first living
documentary of documenting the stories
the lives of
entrepreneurs uh we aim uh to document
the stories of
entrepreneurs uh and also our aim is to
give free education so you know how you
see some of the those entrepreneurs that
want to give you the secrets of success
and they want you to pay $99.97 for it
well we are giving away free education
um with the collaboration of all the
entrepreneurs that we work with so um
you know this is definitely a great
project and then of course uh we we want
to develop future entrepreneurs we want
to encourage more people to get into
business um for themselves um and that
stems from documenting the stories like
such as our guest that we're going to
have today and then the last and and and
and not least um point is that we want
to create honest content honest content
meaning um content that um is fact
checked I mean when people are talking
we we want to display comments on the
the screen and allow you guys to put in
information so that we can address it if
someone's not saying anything that is
factual so we are working on this um
this project and actually you know I'm
going to be working trying to develop
some AI technology so that we can
actually pull up facts as they come up
on the screen but for the time being we
need your guys' help and support to do
so so um that those are the four points
of of uh of of the hustle Zone and then
uh we have a GoFundMe campaign um you
know to do all of this stuff uh we need
your help um because this uh this
project is is being funded by myself and
it has been for the last year um and it
looks like Facebook doesn't want to
display my comments today and that's
okay I will have to figure out another
way to go about this so um just one
second just got a notification that they
won't uh display my comments but anyway
um so ww. gofundme.com
hustlez own.tv
and um uh and then where are where do
all the funds go
Ryan I want to know where my money goes
well we put a graph together so 50 50%
it's not 51% we're going to change that
graphic we'll go to hiring employees um
you know to to put put together the
graphic design and all those Services
together um um and having writers uh
write content and and help us document
these stories we're also going to be
traveling and interviewing entrepreneurs
and then of course we're going to be
investing in techn techology um in order
for us to um to to to keep ahead of the
curve and to produce some great content
uh so um that's that's pretty much it so
today's
guest had me on his
show um he had me on his show I believe
it was probably several several months
ago and um I really enjoyed being on his
show you know he was a you know no one
you know like he was one probably one of
the first people to actually invite me
on to the show I don't know what what it
is about Ryan Perez why people don't
want to invite me I invite everybody
everybody come on my show but nobody
wants to invite me on their show um but
he was one of the first people to
actually to actually invite me on the
show because I mean it's it's fun it's
one thing to actually um it's one thing
to do the hustle Zone and to like cuz I
have a specific script and specific
topics I talk about but no one really
knows the man behind the entrepreneur
and he helped he you know by bringing me
on to his show um he gave people a
different side to me so I'm forever
grateful um uh for having him on the
show or for H for H for him having me on
the show and then I'm grateful that he
he wanted to come on to this show um and
uh so he's going to be talking about his
company the water filter warehouse and
then of course of course folks of course
he's going to be talking to us about um
about uh the uh hold on one second now
Dan is not coming out pretty okay yeah
and then of course he's going to be
talking to us about his story so um
ladies and
gentlemen give it up for Dan the
Waterman how are you doing my
friend I'm doing good I'm doing good so
uh uh you are out and about where where
are you right now where are you what are
you doing this
live can you say that one more Point
again you yeah it clipped
out somewhere with Wi-Fi because I'm an
hour from my house so oh okay so you're
you're an hour from your house so okay
um it looks really nice and sunny out
there I'm I'm I'm uh I'm pretty jealous
of the amount of uh weather that you
guys have out there in Florida so like
what's the weather like right now it's
82 degrees sunny breezy got like kind of
like a cool breeze man it's awesome down
here this is why people move to Florida
the Summers here suck but this is why
people move this is why people move to
Florida well I I you you Pro I'm going
to be your neighbor U we'll we'll sell
water together because like it's so cold
I went out for my birthday yesterday and
it was super duper duper cold um so Dan
um the first question that normally when
people come onto the hustle Zone the
first question that I ask them is what
is your story so leading up to your
success and and whatnot tell us even
from when you were a kid what you know
as far as you can remember tell us you
know who you are where you grew up you
know um you know where you went to
school and and all those those good
things yeah man so I was born in Jersey
um my dad was in the military so we
moved around a lot but we settled down
in Virginia and that's where I went to
elementary school and middle
school in Northfolk Virginia and then we
uh my mom got remarried and we moved to
a place called the Eastern Shore which
is literally the middle of nowhere in
Virginia where is where where I went to
high school so um from middle school on
I remember selling stuff so Bubblicious
bubblegum candy bars Jolly
Ranchers um you know whatever whatever I
could sell um and then in high school I
uh I started a business when I was in
high school delivering food um then we
had 18 different contracts I couldn't
legally open a business so I had to get
a friend of mine that was old enough to
open a business um so we had 18
different contracts with 18 restaurants
that we delivered food for so we were
one of the
first um we are one of the first
companies that there's tons of them out
there now but uh one of the first
companies that actually delivered food
for restaurants oh
wow and and how H how old were you when
you uh were doing this 17
17 wow okay so carry
on um so we did we did really really
well I was 17 making you know 2500 three
grand a week um started college when I
was 17 and I remember asking my
professor how much money he made because
I thought you know he's a business
professor he owns a couple businesses
he's you know he's teaching us all how
to be successful when he told me he made
$80,000 a year and I quit college that
day okay say that again you you quit
okay hold on hold on hold on back it
up so at 17 you went to college yeah and
while this business is is running you
just decided I'm going to quit school
yep that's insane so how did how did
that make you feel at that time about
school like like what was the decision
that what was the decision making in
your in your head like how did was it an
emotional decision or you know did you
just know that it was the right thing to
do kind of both
um I'm a very uh impulsive person to be
honest with you so I uh as soon as I
heard how much he made I said you know
what I'm not here to make $80,000 a year
and back then you know you know 2002
2003 $80,000 of a year was decent money
now it's really not that much now
um but uh it I just made the decision to
do it it I was happy for about a week
and then our uh our company actually
went out of business like two weeks
later well okay hold on on a second okay
sirry you're company went out of
business two weeks later and in
literally 30 minutes so here's what
happened when you're in college who do
you hire you hire College people right
so we were a food delivery
company one one Friday night we had 98
deliveries right and all of our delivery
drivers decided to go to a party instead
of come to work so we lost every single
contract because in the Clause of the
contract we could not default within the
first 30 days of being um or 60 days
excuse me me of being associated with
that restaurant so um in literally 30
minutes we lost every single contract
because we couldn't handle the the
delivery
so I decided to move to Florida to sell
water
treatment
okay okay this is confusing
so you left
school you lost your business yep and
then you decided to move to Florida to
sell water okay where's the I I'm having
a hard time piecing this story together
what what caused you to move to Florida
and sell
water my dad was doing it so my dad did
it for 23 years um and since I was
younger I would just I would come down
to Florida and visit and run
appointments run leads with them see how
bad the water was and he said hey you
know you're not doing anything why don't
you come down to Florida and sell water
treatment so I've been here for 14
years okay and so you you've have you
been working with your
dad I was I
was and to be to be transparent working
with family is very difficult so um if
you're in the situation where you're
working with family make sure you can
differentiate personal and business okay
so um so that sounds like you had some
you had some riffs and um you know had
some conversations with your dad that
you probably you probably regret now
when you look back but what were what
what were kind of the the conversations
that you were having um or the you know
the frustrations that you were having in
working with your dad cuz you know I
know what it's like cuz my dad and I I
started doing graphic design for him um
for his band and we would get in so much
fights all the time because you know he
can't separate being my father and being
you know a business person right so um
what were some of the issues or
frustrations that you had um in working
with your dad and exactly what you're
talking about you
know it's very easy for
um I wouldn't say take advantage of but
it's very easy to pay someone that is
blood a little bit of money to do a
certain job so some of the issues we had
was you know me doing a ton of the work
bringing in a lot of the revenue and
getting paid the least of anybody in the
company so
um no you were getting s you were paying
you you were getting paid the
least um the least amount in the company
so he was kind of like using you as free
free
labor pretty much and um you know and
and that's quite common right especially
when you get your girlfriend or you know
someone working in your business you're
like you going going to make a
dollar but I need you to work the best
and I need you to work late and I need
you to work early in the morning and all
that good stuff so that got pretty
frustrating with you so how how did you
resolve that started my own
company uh how how how soon did you how
how soon did you start the company and
and
um uh so yeah I think it's really
important to know what you know and what
I mean by that is know where your
boundaries are for running a business so
I knew how to sell right but I didn't
know didn't know how to work on water
treatment equipment I didn't know how to
service equipment I didn't know how to
deal with financing so I went and worked
for another company for three years so I
could learn all that stuff um so I took
a position with a major water filtration
company um and learn the finance aspect
learn how to do installs learn how to uh
service equipment learned every other
aspect of the business I didn't know so
when it was time for me to go out on my
I teach people how to do aspect of the
business how how you know with starting
a business like did you have money set
aside for you to do that or how did you
how did you get financing to do any of
that um not really um to be transparent
I got I borrowed a little bit of money
from a friend of mine
um and uh and I put that money towards
equipment because I knew I could sell it
so I just needed to uh to buy equipment
so I had equipment I could sell um and I
had to front all the cost up front for
install install Parts bought a truck all
that kind of stuff so um it wasn't a lot
of money and it didn't go very far but
we've been in business for uh I guess
officially three months and we did
$80,000 this month in
business8 ,000 wow and did you predict
that that was going to happen did you
you know uh because a lot of people you
know when they start their own business
it's pretty risky right and um um and no
one really talks about the Blood Sweat
and Tears that goes behind it but when
you have a successful business and
you're doing you know you know
significantly good within the 3 months
you know um did you have an idea that
that would happen you know did you
predict or like did you predict for the
worst no I didn't predict the worst
I I knew it was going to work um and I
knew it was going to work because of the
people that I had already surrounded
myself with
um we went from literally in a two guys
me and my partner working together on
this business too now we have seven guys
out in the field three of them are
starting this week they're going to be
done their sales training and they're
going to be we'll do $150,000 in
September that's crazy that's insane and
um what did your dad say when when you
know you know your dad like you know did
he you know how did that all work itself
out he he's he'll always be a
micromanager so you know he's he wants
to try to be involved even though he's
not love him to death but yeah they
well you know and and and my dad does
the same thing too and and and you know
parents and being a parent you know you
always worry about your children you
always want your children to do well and
you always see things um in your
children that they don't see but they
kind of have to go through their own
thing and but you get you know but I can
understand even from the other part with
my dad you know telling me that you need
to Market like he was saying Ryan you
need to get out there just yesterday
okay you need to get you need to get out
there and I'm like but Dad I'm already
out there you know what I mean like so
it it's it's it's pretty rough but you
know the fact that you know you love
your parents and um you know and you
always love them you have unconditional
love for them but it sometimes it gets
frustrating so um when you were growing
up did were did you have a lot of
friends did were did did you um you know
you seem to be a smart guy and usually
smart guys are you know by themselves
kind of thinking and tinkering stuff
when they're kids and not really
associate with a lot of people were you
that person or were you the opposite
where did you have a lot of friends did
you have a lot of support when you were
growing
up I think in each because I like I said
we moved around a little bit so in each
area I moved I had like two or three
really good friends I didn't really have
anybody that you know didn't like me
yeah but I wasn't like that guy that you
know went to all these parties and had
aot you know you know what I mean so I
had a um I had two or three people that
I used you know in each aspect of life
that I would hang out with or you know
do stuff with and every single one of
them at this point is pretty successful
so I was hanging out with the right
people at a young age how did you know
these were the right people I mean um
there's so many kids I mean 600 kids in
one high school how would you know to
pick up the runs that you know were were
were good influences and that went off
to do great things at that age I had no
idea man just you know like-minded
people kind of tend to tend to find each
other like kind of like me and you have
so
um I don't think there was any type of
uh you
know formula to finding the right people
to hang out with when I was six yeah it
was just I guess you know I guess it's
just your demeanor and the sort of
things that you were interested in you
know you kind of attract the right
people and then they they go off to do
great things and um you know which is
great now did you ever have problems in
schools especially moving around like
did that ever affect you in in any way
personally not
really
um I I moved from elementary middle
school I went to the same school and
then we moved in high school so I mean
adjusting to a new area I was I grew up
in the city and then we moved to the
country that I think that was a bigger
adjustment than going to a new school is
moving to the moving to the country and
and why was that such a big adjustment
for
you where what do you live in a city yes
I live in a city but we have a lot of
country so um but I mean I understand
but you know from your point of view
what what I went from a from a a middle
school that had like 2,000 kids in it to
a high school that literally had like a
hundred people in
it
um I think the fact that everybody knew
everything about every single person in
that school it was it was just it was
different you know everybody in high
school I knew
everybody you couldn't get away with
anything not that I was trying to get
away with stuff but you could you
couldn't do anything where we lived and
everybody not know about it and did that
did that like did that cause problems uh
did that cause problems for you in high
school um because cuz I'm a very like
I'm an introvert and I I don't like it
when you know even though people think
I'm very outgoing and out there I'm
actually the the opposite so when
there's personal things about me out
there I don't like it um you know when
people talking stuff behind my back or
whatever I don't like that you know that
feeling and like how did you did like
but you seem to be very very Mello head
headed guy and um you seem to be able to
just shift through a lot of stuff you
know with your demeanor but did you have
any complications with that at
all um not really I mean I had a couple
people that we didn't I didn't really
get along with but MH
um not really man I was just you know
hung out with the people that I hung out
with and did what we did when when we
were in high school and I played
Sports so I think most people that play
sports are genuinely
liked yeah and and sports now like you
know kind of creating a segue here into
your new business ventures but you know
Sports is really good at really building
teams and understanding teamwork and and
and Leadership and and stuff like that
did that did that help you a lot when
you were in
sports
absolutely absolutely what were you oh
go ahead go ahead go ahead no you go
ahead so so our company now I don't look
at it as I'm the CEO you work for me I
look at is we're all the same team we
move as one one organization one unit we
all have one goal I don't need to
babysit everybody if I need a babysit
you don't need to be on the team so
that's kind of like what it was I played
soccer and football so in soccer and
football if you didn't hold your own
weight you didn't play you were on the
bench or you were or you weren't on the
team so it's very similar in
business just a special shout out to
Monica uh cardoo in the house uh uh
what's going on Monica uh please share
this out uh Facebook is doing something
really weird they have a bug so I'm
unable to display the comments today um
but please share this out and we're
going to do this after the the broadcast
as well but yeah okay so you've you've
you've um um you know you played Sports
now going back to where you are now um
you've recently started a
podcast uh and two different types of
podcasts can you tell us a little bit
about them so entrepreneur Boulevard I
started 6 months ago um and the reason I
started it was because I was terrified
to go live on
Facebook really anywhere where I was on
video I was terrified of so what better
way to get over a fear or get past a
roadblock or something that you don't
like doing then to start a show and
interview people
live why were you
terrified when why I don't know man I
think I was worried about
like you know what people thought about
me what I was going to say because there
was there's a lot of people out out
there on Facebook that go live and they
don't talk
they talk right right but talk about
anything so I
was it was kind of like I was talking to
myself when I was going live there was
no like person to interact with
right so I knew I I had stuff to say but
I was worried about how it would come
out how people would perceive it if I
said something wrong it was live so I
couldn't go back and unsay it
um so I just started reaching out to
some pretty successful entrepreneurs and
so interviewing about what it took to
get where they're
at and and it's kind of the same format
as the hustle Zone and some other shows
that we've seen where you know we're
talking to entrepreneurs trying to
understand the story I mean you can't
get enough of hearing people's stories
because you know there's always little
nuggets and stuff like that that you can
uh you can pick up on um why did you
decide to go live anyways like what was
the inclination for you to start doing
it because it was a comfort zone that I
hadn't um I hadn't gotten over it I
hadn't gotten past
it so I don't like Comfort zones so
whether it's knocking on doors and
business which a lot of people are
terrified to do yeah or live on Facebook
I just decided to do it so I decided to
do it one day and that day I interviewed
I think Jeremy rubben the friendly
flipper was my first
interview
wow that's amazing and did you know him
before no
I actually saw him on uh on Powerhouse
because he was one of the original
members of Powerhouse yeah which is what
co-host of Powerhouse now um so he was
one of the original original members and
he always brought value every time he
went live and he used to be scared to go
live so like I'll just interview him
about you know his business the friendly
flipper Academy he had he hadn't
launched it yet and uh I wanted to bring
value to the audience but also bring
value to him as far as maybe helping him
get some
[Music]
business okay well that's that's awesome
and um you know tell us a little bit
about uh uh the Water Filter
Warehouse dude we sell everything water
shower filters sink filters water
pictures whole house water
filtration for a hospital a mall
anything water we we do so if you you
want a specific chemical remove from the
water we can do it if you want something
put in the water we can do it um we are
a full service water filtration company
I mean we've been in business for
officially three months I guess I've
owned other businesses along the way and
I still own a couple businesses online
but
water sorry water filter wareh herself
has been in business um really since
August
um you know we already have 100 five
star reviews we have thousands of
customers around the country we're doing
really really well that's awesome do you
do business in Canada absolutely that's
crazy so and then how how big is your
Warehouse uh we don't have a warehouse
It's virtual it's a virtual Warehouse
yeah man we we we stock some stuff
locally but we don't really have to a
lot of it like our we our bread and
butter is residential local residential
business whole house water filtration
reverse house mosis drinking water
systems um but online we drop ship
everything geez so you're just lit
literally like do you do you even go
into work like do you have like an
office that you go into or do you you do
you run this from your home or like I
have an off home but by January we're at
the point right now we have to get an
office for for for training purposes for
recruiting for meetings for customers
for
organization you know we have to have an
office okay that's awesome now do you
have kids and um wife and all that good
stuff I got a circus in my
house tell us a little about about your
family we have four
boys um I've been we've been married
Taisha and I have been married 10 years
um we have four boys 7 five two and 11
months and
uh it's a lot of work awesome and so
it's a lot of work now how does your you
know I we we don't normally um a lot of
us don't really talk about our
relationships with our spouses
especially with comes to business
because we don't want to reveal the
times where we're working a little bit
too late and they're like come to bed no
I got to work you know we don't really
have those conversations right and um um
you okay Betsy did you did why did you
spend the credit card you know like well
I just we just need a new shower
curtains we don't really talk about
those sort of things but they happen in
relationships right um so are like when
it comes to business and relationships
have you had to deal with you know some
issues with you working too late working
too hard or did you you know kind of go
in this you know making sure that you
always had the balance
there's always there's always going to
be a juggling because family should
always come first right but how do you
provide for that you provide for that
family by working so you have to make
sure that the time you are working is
really productive the benefit of being
an entrepreneur working for yourself is
you can work around certain things like
not start working until one o'clock or 2
o'clock or whatever work on Saturday or
Sunday but
I'm a workaholic
so um of course we we there's there's
there's going to be issues with me
working too much and we're trying to
find that that happy medium because I do
want to spend more time with the family
but I want to spend more time with the
family doing stuff that some people
aren't able to do because of the work I
put in right so there's a there's a
balancing act so do do you ever find
though um because I mean I was put in
that situation I worked a lot I've
always been a hard worker um just
recently got into you know a
relationship and whatnot but I kind of
spent four years really pounding the
pavement and and whatnot and you know my
relationship with my ex- fiance broke up
because you know losing love falling out
of love and um because I'm working too
much and that I'm and here I'm thinking
everything's fine you know let's go here
let's travel here let's do here do or go
there or whatever ever um and then it um
you know but it didn't turn out well so
are you ever afraid that you know
working too hard may cause that within
your relationship and knock on would I'm
not saying that it would but like do you
ever have those fears and do you have a
contingency plan to ensure that you know
that doesn't
happen H I guess the answer would be no
I'm not I'm not worried about that
because um we have an agreement that you
know my wife doesn't work we're blessed
enough to be able to homeschool our kids
my wife homeschools two of our kids
right um so the only way that that is
going to work is if I'm making enough
money right yeah so she realizes that
sometimes I have to work you know until
one two three four in the morning right
um but there's also that happy medium
you know I usually don't work week
unless it's an absolute
emergency I'm available for our team
members I'm available um to coach but
I'm not I typically won't go run an
appointment or you know go into my
office at home and and do work I'm
typically spending the time with the
family so right now quick question for
you now we're gonna we have one more
question and it's a really deep question
and then we're going to go into our
lightning
round um but um so if you were
to if something bad would happen like
you you get into a car accident or you
get into a serious accident or have a
health
complication how would your business run
and would you like would you have a
system in place to um to to to allow it
to run without you because I know that's
uh I think right now we're in an
automation world right now where things
are becoming more automated and and
whatnot and are you confident that you
know in situations where you have to go
on a vacation that you don't need to go
back to work do you know what I mean and
you don't have to stop everything to go
and and deal with you know complications
um from your business right so I have a
business
partner he's a really really good friend
of mine and the group of guys that we
have that we've that we've brought on
our team I have no doubt that if I were
to leave production would probably go up
I'm saying that jokingly because I do
micromanage a little bit right but I
think they would
um they have to provide for their
families they have a job to do they have
stuff to sell right right so if I'm not
there whether I'm here or not they still
have to provide they still have to make
money so the guys that we've selected to
be on our team I have no doubt that they
would it would still run successfully I
could leave right now and it would run
and it would and it do
well did you just say what I heard you
thought I heard you say you said that if
you left the
business it would do more because you
micromanage little like K now you just
said your father
micromanages and then and you're using
the same tactics on your employees no
not the same not the same okay a little
bit little bit of micromanagement and
why and and and and that must be your
thing so why is it your
thing I don't like being micromanaged
yeah there's certain people that you
have to micromanage right
and they're going to be successful
without you micromanaging them right but
with you helping them or coaching them
consistently and micromanaging a little
bit and keeping your thumb on them just
a tiny bit and pushing them they will
find a new level of
success and everybody has to have that
have you ever been in a situation where
you just let things flow you know
like um you know right now while we're
on this
interview well we'll we'll get this this
interview wrapped up so that you can get
back to micromanaging a little bit
but uh we're going to go into our
lightning round here and then we're
going to end the show so um I'm going to
ask you some questions um just to get a
little you know uh just to know uh some
different things about you so are you uh
more of a hunter or a
gatherer
Hunter you are a new addition to the
crayon box what color would you be in y
blue water
uh we finished the interview we finished
the interview and you stepped out of the
office and found a lottery ticket that
ends up winning $10 million uh what
would you
do H buy Bitcoin buy Bitcoin no I don't
know there there's a you know there's
the the the Bitcoin hype right now I own
a little bit of Bitcoin but um I would
invest it in the business invest it back
into the business um Michael Jackson or
Prince Michael Jackson uh what's your
favorite 90s
Jam H I was just listening to 90s uh uh
hipop on the way over to do this
interview so 50 Cent happened to be on
so I don't know that that's my favorite
but I mean there's just so many so many
great artists from the 90s f i yeah uh
what's the last gift someone gave you
last a
watch uh and uh what's your favorite
dessert H pumpkin pie pumpkin pie uh
what were you like in high
school the same as I am
now micro a tad bit micromanager okay I
get that um any advice for your previous
boss quit move the
far far
away and what do you want um what's the
funniest thing that um has what's the
funniest thing that has happened to you
recently the funniest thing
happened I don't know man work related
or personal it doesn't matter does
someone fall hit their head
no I mean my kids are always
saying uh stuff that's fun so last night
I'll just use this because I liked it so
last night my son Daniel he uh I think
he was sleeping and he looks at me he
said daddy do you know what a100 $100
bills are 10 grand I don't know that's
funny
but that the fact that my seven-year-old
knows that 100 times 100 is 10,000 bucks
I'm I'm happy about that oh yeah oh yeah
like kids say the darnest things man and
and like we were I was working with uh
my son yesterday and it's not a funny
story but like we were cuz he has disc
calculus so I was working out math
and I like the you know do you know
Common Core I don't know if anyone knows
common Corp
but that is horrible for kids that's
part of why we
homeschool it's like they make extra
it's just extra garbage right for uh you
know to to teach kids so I taught him
the way that I learned and he's like I
got it you know he's like Dad I'm smart
you know he's like I'm gonna go to the
teachers tomorrow and I'm gonna you know
and and I was so happy like it's not a
funny story but it was just happy to see
him you know be empowered to go back to
school and tell the teacher off because
I mean uh like the the kind of that
they're teaching these children excuse
my language is ridiculous yeah but um
but anyway I I I concluded if I could
cap if I could capture my kids facial
expressions like two of my kids Joshua
and Matthew their facial
expressions crazy crazy funny like I
I'll see if I can post one on my wall
later tonight when I get home some their
facial
expressions
funny awesome well I'm gonna conclude
this interview thank you so much how was
your experience on the hustle Zone by
the way you being in the podcast
business and all kinds of things I love
man I love the lightning round the
lightning round yeah that's a little bit
more uh positive and you know uh but
yeah you know we we try our best to
reveal more you know like everyone has
very specific questions that they ask on
their on their shows but we want we
don't want to compete with people we
want to just provide additional context
so you know we ask the deeper questions
we want to know a little bit more about
you and and you know it's even even for
me like you and I don't know each other
but we got to know a little bit about
each other just through this interview
so you know I I do thank you for for
coming on to the show and um you know
but before you go there's one more
tradition um the tradition
is I do a call and response and then I
say welcome to the and then you have to
scream hustle Zone really loud so like
I've had people do it in public I've had
people do it in their homes when their
wives are sleeping and their children
they got new horns um so you're going to
have to scream it
loud he's already
getting so okay so um let's get ready
oh so look I'm get me okay okay all
right so I'm gonna say welcome to the
and you need to say hustle on okay
so welcome to the
hustle
Zone that was good it was in the car got
like all the on Beyonds of the car as
well like thank you so much um uh Dan
for for coming in onto the hustle Zone I
really do appreciate it and um I'm going
to send you uh the link uh once the the
show is posted but but but feel free
since we didn't uh it was today like
it's really hard because like it I don't
know Facebook froze so if we can send
this out to all of our friends and
family that would be great and thank you
guys all for participating couldn't put
your comments on the screen we're
working on it um but I will talk to you
guys soon thank you guys all for uh for
coming into the hustle Zone and any last
words
Dan no man you keep
rocking okay awesome all right well talk
to you later Dan and um and folks I um
so folks make sure again to uh check us
out on uh uh Bai creative this is
sponsored by Bai creative and it
is branding jim.com and of course this
is bow TI this is ww. hustlez own.tv
and we definitely want you guys
to go to our GoFundMe and
donate uh and and you could see the the
breakdown of our you know donation
schemes and and all that good stuff so
it's gofundme.com
uh hustle Zone hyphen TV so thank you
guys all for participating in the hustle
Zone and I will talk to you guys later
[Music]